export const topick5 = [
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the legendary sea creature associated with Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Kraken',
      b: 'Sea Serpent',
      c: 'Siren',
    },
    answer: 'Sea Serpent',
  },
  {
    question: 'What legend is associated with the lighthouse of Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Ghost of a captain',
      b: 'Ghost ship',
      c: 'Pirate treasure',
    },
    answer: 'Ghost ship',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What mythical island was supposedly seen by sailors off the coast of Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Treasure Island',
      b: 'Island of the Sirens',
      c: 'El Dorado Island',
    },
    answer: 'El Dorado Island',
  },
  {
    question: 'What legend is associated with the fish market of Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Golden fish',
      b: 'Silver shark',
      c: 'Bronze crab',
    },
    answer: 'Golden fish',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which mythical sea god, according to legend, protected Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Poseidon',
      b: 'Neptune',
      c: 'Triton',
    },
    answer: 'Neptune',
  },
  {
    question: 'What legend explains the origin of the sand dunes near Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Giants piled them up',
      b: 'Sailors poured sand',
      c: 'They grew from sea foam',
    },
    answer: 'Giants piled them up',
  },
  {
    question: 'What myth is associated with the fishermen of Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'They could talk to dolphins',
      b: 'They caught golden fish',
      c: 'They were immortal',
    },
    answer: 'They could talk to dolphins',
  },
  {
    question: 'What legend is associated with the coastline of Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'It was created by a sea dragon',
      b: 'It was protected by magical forces',
      c: 'It was a place of hidden treasures',
    },
    answer: 'It was protected by magical forces',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What mythical captain supposedly sailed off the coast of Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Captain Nemo',
      b: 'Captain Sea Wolf',
      c: 'Captain Silver',
    },
    answer: 'Captain Sea Wolf',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What legend is associated with the underwater caves near Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'Pirate treasures are hidden in them',
      b: 'They lead to an underwater city',
      c: 'Sea monsters live in them',
    },
    answer: 'Pirate treasures are hidden in them',
  },
];
